<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Mark Petherbridge</title>
    <link>https://markpetherbridge.co.uk/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Mark Petherbridge</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Developing with &lt;i class=&#39;fas fa-heart&#39;&gt;&lt;/i&gt; and &lt;i class=&#39;fas fa-mug-hot&#39;&gt;&lt;/i&gt; in Japan</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 12 Apr 2020 16:13:03 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="https://markpetherbridge.co.uk/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
          <title>How to Install Elusive Sublime Babel VS Code plugin (3 steps)</title>
          <link>https://markpetherbridge.co.uk/blog/how-to-install-sublime-babel/</link>
          <pubDate>Sun, 12 Apr 2020 16:13:03 &#43;0900</pubDate>
          
          <guid>https://markpetherbridge.co.uk/blog/how-to-install-sublime-babel/</guid>
          <description>I recently have been getting to grips with Reach Native as I am working on a new app project for a client. Like most &amp;ldquo;new to a framework&amp;rdquo; developers I first typed into Google &amp;ldquo;How to build a React Native App&amp;rdquo;. Favoring videos I switched to Youtube and found a Net ninja special course. Yay.
However, like most media on the net, especially videos. They often out-date very quickly, recommended packages and software is no longer available and updates (especially JS frameworks) are so often that you really can fall behind quickly.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Codility Challenge: My Binary Gap Positive Integer Solution (Python)    </title>
          <link>https://markpetherbridge.co.uk/blog/codility-binary-gap-positive-integer-solution/</link>
          <pubDate>Mon, 23 Mar 2020 10:35:16 &#43;0900</pubDate>
          
          <guid>https://markpetherbridge.co.uk/blog/codility-binary-gap-positive-integer-solution/</guid>
          <description>The task Smaller pieces are easier to digest So how do we do that in Python? And that sums up the breakdown of the code.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>An Elementary and Slightly Distilled Introduction to Blockchain</title>
          <link>https://markpetherbridge.co.uk/blog/an-elementary-and-slightly-distilled-introduction-to-blockchain/</link>
          <pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2019 11:13:25 &#43;0900</pubDate>
          
          <guid>https://markpetherbridge.co.uk/blog/an-elementary-and-slightly-distilled-introduction-to-blockchain/</guid>
          <description>Blockchain, you have heard of it right? It&amp;rsquo;s the one that is more notably recognised as being synonymously linked to cryptocurrencies such as Bitcoin. Its popularity boomed towards the end of 2017 when the first Bitcoin peaked at its all-time high price of around $20k. Some people became very rich indeed and this spurred on the outburst of blockchain development companies, apps, games, online communities, whale investors and of course media coverage.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>How to Increase Upload Limit for All in One Wp Migration Plugin</title>
          <link>https://markpetherbridge.co.uk/blog/how-to-increase-upload-limit-for-all-in-one-wp-migration-plugin/</link>
          <pubDate>Sun, 03 Feb 2019 12:03:57 &#43;0900</pubDate>
          
          <guid>https://markpetherbridge.co.uk/blog/how-to-increase-upload-limit-for-all-in-one-wp-migration-plugin/</guid>
          <description>Sometimes you need to do some work quickly, and a manual WordPress migration is not known for being easy. This is where plugins like All-in-One WP Migrationcome in handy. However, at the moment there is a very small upload limit and if you are not in a position to pay for the upgrade or just don&amp;rsquo;t have the time there is a very quick hack you can do to increase the limit.</description>
        </item>
        
  </channel>
</rss>
